{
  "decadeGameData": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "title": "Decade Trivia",
      "categories": [
        {
          "id": "1-1",
          "categorytitle": "1950s",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": "1-1-1",
              "question": "The famous rock and roll artist released the hit song \"Rock Around the Clock\" in 1954?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Who is Bill Haley & His Comets?"
            },
            {
              "id": "1-1-2",
              "question": "This historic Supreme Court case declared racial segregation in public schools unconstitutional?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "What is Brown v. Board of Education?"
            },
            {
              "id": "1-1-3",
              "question": "The leader of the Soviet Union during the majority of the 1950s was?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Who is Nikita Khrushchev?"
            },
            {
              "id": "1-1-4",
              "question": "The popular television show premiered in 1951 and featured Lucille Ball?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "What is I Love Lucy?"
            },
            {
              "id": "1-1-5",
              "question": "The name of the famous bus boycott that took place in Montgomery, Alabama, in 1955 was?",
              "level": "hard",
              "answer": "What is Montgomery Bus Boycott?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1-2",
          "categorytitle": "1960s",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": "2-2-1",
              "question": "The winner of the Best Picture at the Academy Awards in 1960 is ",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "What is The Apartment?"
            },
            {
              "id": "2-2-2",
              "question": "The military conflict that the United States was involved in during the 1960s and 1970s is ",
              "level": "hard",
              "answer": "What is the Vietnam War?"
            },
            {
              "id": "2-2-3",
              "question": "The first man to walk on the moon is ",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Who is Neil Armstrong?"
            },
            {
              "id": "2-2-4",
              "question": "This famous music festival took place in upstate New York in 1969?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "What is Woodstock?"
            },
            {
              "id": "2-2-5",
              "question": "This political leader was assassinated in Dallas, Texas, in 1963?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "Who is John F. Kennedy?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1-3",
          "categorytitle": "1970s",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": "3-3-1",
              "question": "This actor played the iconic character Rocky Balboa in the film \"Rocky\" released in 1976?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Who is Sylvester Stallone?"
            },
            {
              "id": "3-3-2",
              "question": "This movie was the highest-grossing film of the 1970s?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "What is Star Wars?"
            },
            {
              "id": "3-3-3",
              "question": "This American president resigned from office in 1974?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "Who is Richard Nixon?"
            },
            {
              "id": "3-3-4",
              "question": "This American serial killer terrorized California in the late 1960s and early 1970s?",
              "level": "hard",
              "answer": "Who is the Zodiac Killer?"
            },
            {
              "id": "3-3-5",
              "question": "This disco hit by the Bee Gees was featured in the film \"Saturday Night Fever\" released in 1977?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "What is Stayin' Alive?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1-4",
          "categorytitle": "1980s",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": "4-4-1",
              "question": "The first female British Prime Minister was?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Who is Margaret Thatcher?"
            },
            {
              "id": "4-4-2",
              "question": "This iconic handheld gaming device was released by Nintendo in 1989?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "What is Game Boy?"
            },
            {
              "id": "4-4-3",
              "question": "The highest-grossing film of the 1980s was?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "What is E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial?"
            },
            {
              "id": "4-4-4",
              "question": "This famous album by Michael Jackson was released in 1982?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "What is Thriller?"
            },
            {
              "id": "4-4-5",
              "question": "This popular dance style that emerged in the 1980s is known for its robotic movements?",
              "level": "hard",
              "answer": "What is Breakdancing?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1-5",
          "categorytitle": "1990s",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": "5-5-1",
              "question": " This popular sitcom featured six friends living in New York City?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "What is Friends?"
            },
            {
              "id": "5-5-2",
              "question": "This female artist released the hit song \"Baby One More Time\" in 1998?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "Who is Britney Spears?"
            },
            {
              "id": "5-5-3",
              "question": "The name of the highest-grossing animated film of the 1990s is?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "What is The Lion King?"
            },
            {
              "id": "5-5-4",
              "question": "The American president who signed the North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) into law in 1993 is?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "Who is Bill Clinton?"
            },
            {
              "id": "5-5-5",
              "question": "The conflict between Iraq and a coalition led by the United States in the early 1990s is?",
              "level": "hard",
              "answer": "What is the Gulf War?"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1-6",
          "categorytitle": "2000s",
          "questions": [
            {
              "id": "6-6-1",
              "question": "This social media platform was founded by Mark Zuckerberg in 2004?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "What is Facebook?"
            },
            {
              "id": "6-6-2",
              "question": "The name of the first smartphone released by Apple in 2007 is?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "What is the iPhone?"
            },
            {
              "id": "6-6-3",
              "question": "The Academy Award for Best Actor winner for his role in the film \"Ray\"released in 2004 is?",
              "level": "medium",
              "answer": "Who is Jamie Foxx?"
            },
            {
              "id": "6-6-4",
              "question": "This country hosted the 2008 Summer Olympics?",
              "level": "easy",
              "answer": "What is China?"
            },
            {
              "id": "6-6-5",
              "question": "This catastrophic hurricane struck the Gulf Coast of the United States in 2005?",
              "level": "hard",
              "answer": "What is Hurricane Katrina?"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
